[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
Divine Oytengco and Miss Cora are dead.
Now's the time. We have to arm ourselves.
We have to fight back.
Fine, go ahead and kill! Let's all kill!
How will that make us
any different from them?!
Later, you'll have a visitor.
Who are you?!
Why did you bring me here?!
You won't be going to jail.
Who helped me?
What kind of nonsense is this?!
How was Emilia's case whitewashed?!
They got everything.
[Ivy] Who else could've helped Emilia?!
[Julio] Diego's group
is planning to cause trouble again.
And I choose you, Miss Aguas,
to carry out their punishment.
Kill Diego's men.
-No!
-Well, you choose.
Either you kill them, or I'll kill you.
[Ivy] Fine.
If it'll make you happy, I'll do it.
[Jose] You didn't help Emilia?
[Julio] I just want to know who did.
Because one day, that person
might be a threat to us.
[Camia] Who were those men, Damian?
The moment I find out
that you're lying to us,
I will never forgive you.
[Ivy] Diego! Julio's men abducted Anna
and your supporters!
-They're going to kill them!
-Help!
-Get us out!
Ivy!
Finally, I caught you red-handed.
Traitor.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Be careful, okay?
-[Diego panting]
Protect Anna and my daughter.
Yes, Auntie. Don't worry.
Auntie…
Diego Torillo! Stay where you are!
[tense music playing]
Hold on.
What do you need?
Shut up and come with us!
Okay.
Auntie, you take care of everything here.
I'll go with you.
[grunts, groans]
-[Camia yelps]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-[Camia screams]
-[grunts, groans]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[Diego wheezing]
Well?
It's useless, Diego!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Diego panting]
[panting]
So, don't give me that look. Ivy, come on.
Can you just drop the act?
Stop lying to me because I know the truth!
This conspiracy theory thing
was actually true!
Nimfa was right when she said
that you are Diego's spy.
You are Camia and Lily Cruz's
ally, aren't you?
And finally, I see the snake
for what she is!
And worst of all,
you damned woman ruined my son's life!
You ruined my family!
Why did you do this?!
Why, Ivy? Why?!
I don't know what you're talking about.
-[gunshot]
-You liar!
Well?!
Are you still going to lie?
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunting, groaning]
[grunts]
[Emilia] You monster!
[grunting]
You!
-[Emilia grunts]
-[Ivy yelps]
-[Emilia grumbles]
-You monster!
-You damned woman!
-[Ivy grunts]
-Well?!
-Is that all you've got?!
-Admit it!
-[groans]
[panting]
-Just admit it!
-No--
Ouch!
-You nutjob!
-[Emilia whines]
-[grunts, groans]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[grumbles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunting, groaning]
-[labored breathing]
-[panting]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-You traitor!
-[Ivy grunts]
-Admit it!
-[Ivy groans]
You are the traitor in this family!
-[Emilia grumbles]
-[Ivy grunting]
[Emilia grunts]
-[Ivy panting]
-[Emilia groaning]
-You want to hear the truth?
-[Emilia wheezing]
-Answer!
-[groans]
You want to hear it?!
[gasps for air]
Yes, Emilia. It's true!
-[Emilia wheezing]
-I'm the traitor in your family!
I, Ivy Aguas, am the traitor
in the Ardiente family!
[Emilia whines]
I'm allied with Diego, Lily,
and Camia Cruz.
-You hear me, huh?
-[Emilia gasping for air]
I'm the traitor in your family!
-[Emilia grunts]
-I'm the traitor in your family!
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
Stop resisting, Diego!
Camia…
I need to tell you the truth.
[heavy sighing]
I'm not as innocent as I've claimed.
[inhales, exhales]
I…
I am the original Jaguar.
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
-Hey!
-Ah!
-[screaming]
-[grunting]
-[groaning]
[grunting, groaning]
-Hey, you!
-[Camia yelps]
[grunts]
You! [screams]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-Are you okay?!
-Yes.
-Are you sure?
-Get down!
[groans]
[panting]
Diego! Diego!
Get inside. I can handle this.
Auntie.
Get inside!
-[panting]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[coughing]
-Who's going first?!
-Get him!
-Hey!
-[grunts, groans]
[screams]
-[screaming]
-[grunting]
[grunts]
[Camia gasps]
Haven't had enough, huh?!
Wait!
[grunts, groans]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[grunts]
-Gimme that!
Leave!
I said, leave!
Run! Let's go!
-Come on!
-[grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[panting]
-[Julio] Miss Aguas!
-[suspenseful music playing]
Ha!
You can't escape now.
Just give up.
We set the trap and
you jumped right into it.
We told you to kill Diego's people.
But in the process,
Emilia followed you, because we knew that…
you'd rescue those people,
and you wouldn't let them die because…
you really are a traitor.
And we were right all along.
Now…
No snake will leave this place alive.
[sighs]
Colonel.
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunting]
-[Julio grunts]
-[loud thud]
Take her!
[panting]
Are you okay, Damian?
Are you injured?
Mr. Dante?
Diego, no.
He's Damian.
He's Lily's uncle.
Dante is his twin brother.
It's a long story,
but he knows that Ivy is Lily.
[dramatic music playing]
Auntie, I need to go.
Mr. Damian, please take care
of Aunt Camia.
-Diego, be careful.
-I will.
[panting]
[motorcycle engine starts]
[motorcycle engine revving]
Come on.
Let's get inside.
I need water.
[Emilia] Papa!
Papa, wait!
Emilia, you're here?
Yes. I am here, Papa!
And I'm the reason why that snake is here,
and we caught her red-handed!
It's because of me, Papa! Me!
Emilia, no one is taking
the credit away from you.
To tell you the truth…
I'm very proud of you!
Good job!
Good job.
Papa, I don't need your praise.
I need to know where
you're bringing that woman!
[Julio] Wait, wait.
This woman…
does not deserve any special treatment.
There will be no ceremonies.
There will be no rituals.
She will die with a bullet
to the back of her head,
just like any other traitor.
No, Papa! I want to kill her!
-I'll kill her!
-No!
Can you just stop it?!
Take it easy, Emilia.
You know what? That's your problem.
You get so high-strung
that you end up screwing things up.
You can't just kill her here.
It'll leave a lot of evidence against us.
Let the professionals take care of this.
No, Papa. I will kill her!
I will kill that woman
because she's the reason
why Arnaldo went crazy
and why I went to jail!
-I will kill you!
-Please, please!
I am the head of this family.
I will decide how she is going to die.
You may be the head of this family, Papa,
but you're also the reason
why that woman betrayed us!
Because you allowed her
to be close to you!
You sound like a broken record,
repeating yourself.
[Ivy chuckles]
And what is so funny, huh?
What's so funny?!
Look at you two.
You're like two children
fighting over candy.
How about you guys just fight over
who I'm going to kill first
once I get out of this?
-You're getting on my nerves!
-Stop it! Stop it!
-Enough!
-[Emilia groans]
Enough!
You really make my blood boil!
Is that all you can do, Emilia?!
-Enough!
-Come on, Papa!
Don't take this away from me!
We always do what you want!
Now you won't even let me kill her, Papa?!
Come on! I am your daughter!
Give me this chance, Papa!
Put your entitlement issues on the side!
You're such a spoiled brat!
And you, Miss Aguas.
Yes, Governor?
You are mine!
Sure, take me!
I'm all yours.
Sanggano, make sure she doesn't escape.
And take her car with you.
I don't want to leave any evidence.
-Aww, poor Emilia.
-Yes, boss.
Deprived of one more thing.
Well, what's new?
-As always.
-[Emilia groans]
[Ivy grunts]
I will see you in hell!
Can't wait!
I'll roll out the red carpet for you!
Yeah, you should!
Get in!
[Ivy grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
-Damian, give me your hand.
-[Damian groaning]
It hurts.
Oh, ouch, ouch. Be gentle.
-There?
-It hurts.
Damian?
Thank you very much for saving me.
And forgive me for thinking badly of you.
Don't worry about it. I can't blame you
because you know
the stuff I've done before.
And…
I can't say my face
doesn't look suspicious.
Damian…
I wish Dante were still alive…
so he could see how much you've changed.
He always dreamt of seeing you change.
[soft music playing]
[Damian] Now, how am I supposed
to tell you the truth
that I'm a criminal?
That I'm a murderer.
That I am Jaguar.
Where else does it hurt?
I got elbowed here.
You were elbowed?
-It hurts.
-All right.
-Ouch…
-There.
And then, after that, I got hit here.
You were hit there?
Let's put some ice on it.
-Here.
-Ouch. Be gentle.
Hold it.
-Huh?
-Take it.
Let me clean you up.
[soft music playing]
[Loring panting]
Camia!
Oh, Camia!
I thought we wouldn't get out--[gasps]
Oh, thank goodness you're all safe.
Uh…
Oh!
-Miss Loring, Mr. Pandoy…
-Loring?
Anna…
This is Damian, Dante's brother.
Good evening.
[breath quivering]
[Pandoy] Loring?
I thought he was Lily's father.
[Pandoy] Huh?
He looks just like him.
Wait, let's all go inside
so we can clean your wounds.
[pensive music playing]
[motorcycle engine revving]
What happened here?
We don't know.
We just saw the house burning.
Does anyone know what happened here?
No, Diego.
We don't really come here often.
Whose house is this?
We don't know. This is an abandoned house.
No one's lived here for years.
[ominous music playing]
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
-[chains rattling]
-[metal wheels clunking]
[Ivy's breath quivering]
Well, hello, Miss Aguas!
[breath quivering]
Uh… Let's clear things up.
Now that you've been caught…
and are about to die…
Maybe you'll have nothing left
to lose if you tell me…
why you loathe my family so much.
I mean…
What is it that keeps
the fire burning inside you, Miss Aguas?
Did I, or did we, mistreat you
when you were younger?
[suspenseful music playing]
Or did I…
Did I hurt your relatives?
Your parents, perhaps?
Uh… What's your story? Please let me know.
I… [breath quivers]
I have nothing personal
against you, Governor.
[Ivy breathes heavily]
I just want your money and your power.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Weird!
Out of all the powerful
people in the world…
why did you choose my family?
Because you have a psychotic daughter.
And a crazy, obsessive grandson!
I thought it'd be easy.
But I was wrong.
Well, my bad!
Thank you for saying
you underestimated me.
-[Ivy trembling]
-Uh… but…
why do I get the feeling that
everything that comes out of your mouth
is nothing but lies?
Huh?
Well…
It doesn't really matter to me, you know?
Whatever the truth is,
it doesn't really affect me.
Because, after all, you're about to die.
You can bring your secrets to your grave.
But I'm telling you,
I'll be able to sleep soundly…
knowing that you are dead!
[tense music playing]
Enjoy your final hours on Earth,
Miss Aguas!
It was fun going up against you.
And, I must admit…
you were a very worthy opponent.
Goodbye, Your Lying Majesty!
Look who's talking!
Don't celebrate just yet, old man Julio!
Because I'm not through with you!
Where does she get her energy?
[menacing laugh]
-[Ivy's breath quivering]
-[Julio laughs menacingly]
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy was no longer there when I arrived.
And I can't reach her cell phone number.
We couldn't reach her landline
and safehouse numbers, either.
Maybe she's back at the Ardientes' place.
Before we parted ways,
she told me that she'd return
to the Ardientes
so she wouldn't get caught.
But why hasn't she called yet? [huffs]
Auntie, maybe she hasn't
found the chance yet.
I won't be at ease until
I'm sure my daughter's safe!
Auntie Camia, Lily has risked
blowing her cover so many times.
But she always managed
to get out of danger.
If we don't trust Lily,
we might just put her in trouble.
[Loring] Anna is right.
We shouldn't look for Ivy at this point,
or her cover might get blown.
The only thing we can do now is wait.
Waiting isn't an option for me
when it comes to my daughter.
Auntie, don't worry.
I'll come up with another plan
to find her.
[slow tense music playing]
I hate you, Papa. I hate you!
You're so selfish!
You deprived me of everything,
including my real mother!
You always take everything away from me!
Even the chance to kill Ivy Aguas!
It always has to be you!
[inhales sharply]
But this time around,
I won't let things go your way.
I'm not gonna let you do it
because I am going to do it!
I am going to kill Ivy…
…Aguas!
[heavy breathing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Hello, officer.
I would like to report a missing person.
What's their name?
Ivy Aguas.
She went missing on her way
to the Ardientes' place.
We suspect there's foul play involved.
May I know your name?
Just a concerned citizen.
Please go to the Ardientes
and look for Ivy Aguas.
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
How can I help you, gentlemen?
Sorry to bother you, Governor,
but we received a report saying
Miss Ivy Aguas is missing.
[scoffs]
Why?
Does my place look like
a lost-and-found office to you?
I don't know where Miss Aguas is.
I'm no longer associated with her,
so she's not my responsibility.
Perhaps it would be better
for you to look elsewhere.
We're sorry, Governor.
Thank you for your time.
All right.
-Thank you.
I'm sure Diego and his group
are the ones looking for Ivy.
Make sure they don't find her.
Because if that woman breaks free,
I'll make you take her place in her grave.
Yes, Governor.
[Diego] Yes.
Ivy Aguas is on our side.
[indistinct chatter]
She is pretending to help the Ardientes
so she can infiltrate their world.
She is the heart, mind,
and soul of our cause.
And right now…
she could be in danger.
That's why she needs our help.
She needs help from each
and every one of us.
We must find her.
One of us has to stake out
the Ardientes' residence
so we can find out if she's there.
I'll do it, Diego.
-But, son…
-I can do this, Mom.
The Ardientes don't know me.
So, I can move freely
outside their mansion.
A-Are you sure?
It's going to be dangerous.
Miss Aguas risked her life for us.
So, it's only right we return the favor.
I'll help you find her.
Diego.
Leave the search for Ivy to us.
You should focus on stopping
Julio once and for all.
-Yeah.
-That's right.
-I agree!
[tense music playing]
[pensive music playing]
Nanny.
Nanny, is there something wrong?
Hmm?
I noticed you keep looking
at Mister Damian.
Huh?
Well, you see…
he looks exactly like Lily's father.
It makes me recall how Mister Dante
was a very kind man.
He was very brave too.
And that was the reason
the Ardientes had him killed.
I just hope he's as kind as Mister Dante.
I'm sure Lily will be hurt
if he betrays us.
There are so many
deceitful people in the world.
I hope he's not one of them too.
Speaking of deceitful, Mr. Pandoy…
What's our next move against Julio?
I have a plan.
[suspenseful music playing]
Attorney.
Diego.
Vice Governor Ruiz
is already waiting downstairs.
We must convince him
to form an alliance
with us against Julio Ardiente.
Well, Vice Governor Ruiz
does have a reputation
for being intolerant of
corrupt government practices.
You're very much alike, Diego.
Which is why I'm very
confident he'll listen to you.
We can trust him.
I hope so.
Mr. Diego Torillo…
-…and Attorney Fisher.
-Yes?
Vice Governor Ruiz is waiting for you.
Follow me.
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
The Vice Governor's guests.
[knocking on door]
[suspenseful music playing]
[gunshots]
You haven't lost your touch,
Vice Governor.
[suspenseful music playing]
Vice Governor, they're here.
Nurse?
Get Arnaldo dressed. We're going out.
Yes, Governor.
Arnaldo, my grandson…
I have a surprise for you.
We're going to meet…
the woman who hurt you.
-[heart monitor beeping]
-Miss Aguas.
Do you remember her?
I want you to witness her death…
…as revenge for what she did to you.
[foreboding music playing]
[goon] You have to eat, Miss Aguas.
Governor's orders.
Don't try to fight back.
[tense music playing]
[heavy breathing]
Tie her up.
Nice and tight.
Miss Aguas.
Eat up.
-[utensils clanking]
-[groans]
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[grunting, groaning]
-Where's the rope?
-Tie her up!
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey, hurry up.
How many boxes are still there?
Get them.
[line ringing]
Hello?
Miss Camia, I've been here a while now.
But I haven't seen Miss Aguas.
What's going on there?
I think the Ardientes are busy
preparing for the province's
centennial celebration.
Okay, come back now before they catch you.
What about Miss Aguas?
[sighs] I don't think
she's at their mansion.
Go home.
Okay, Miss Camia.
If Lily really were fine,
she would've called ages ago.
What do you think
could've happened to her?
[tense music playing]
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let's get down to business.
We want to file a complaint
to the election commission
about Julio Ardiente's manipulation
of the recent election results.
And we need your support on this.
[sighs]
You see, Diego…
That case is bailable.
Even if you file a case against Julio,
he'll just post bail, and your
efforts will be for nothing.
We've already considered that.
That's why we planned
something big against Julio.
Once this gets out to the public,
he'll be suspended,
and you'll become governor of Ardiente.
You're doing this even though
there's nothing in it for you?
This isn't about my personal ambitions.
It's about obtaining justice
for the people.
So, Vice Governor,
I just want to make sure…
that you're on the people's side.
And that you're ready
to go against the Ardientes.
[pensive music playing]
[slow tense music playing]
-Papa.
-Raul.
Where are you taking Arnaldo?
Oh, just for a little drive.
Don't you think that'll be bad
for his health?
Relax, Raul.
I will take good care of him.
And besides, it'll be better
if he went with me
instead of staying here with you.
[scoffs]
Papa, Arnaldo's my son.
I have the right to decide
whether or not he goes with you.
Then, stop me.
Stop them.
[scoffs] Stop this guy.
I've always had a problem controlling him.
See? He always goes for his gun.
Raul, Raul…
You're the same old Raul as before.
All bark, no bite.
Balls, my boy. Balls.
Try to grow a pair, and you
might just earn my respect
as the father of your son.
Now, if you'll excuse us…
we'll be going now.
Colonel.
[Julio grunts]
-[car engine starts]
-[car door closes]
Ooh!
Madrigal.
What brings you here?
Ma'am…
I'm ready to return the favor now.
You saved me, remember?
What do you want in exchange?
Hmm…
Let me think.
[sexy music playing]
It depends.
What exactly…
…can you do?
Can you make me…
happy?
Give me weapons, ma'am.
And some men.
I'll help you get back at the Ardientes.
I like the idea.
But what about Jaguar?
He almost killed you.
Aren't you interested…
in making him pay for what he did to you?
Aren't you curious
as to who he really is?
As to who the man is
behind that mask?
By the way you talk, ma'am,
you sound like you know him.
[chuckles]
Of course I know who he is.
I'm the reason why he's
roaming free right now.
After all the help I gave him,
he just cast me aside.
In that case,
why don't you tell me who he is?
I can help you.
[slow tense music playing]
Emilia!
-Mr. Raul.
-Emilia!
Sir--
Why'd Emilia let Papa take Arnaldo, huh?!
And you didn't even bother to call me?
Where's Emilia?! Go call her!
She's not here, sir.
She left early.
Where did she go?
I don't know, sir.
Please excuse me.
[tense music playing]
Uh-uh-uh…
Not that fast, Madrigal.
Hmm…
It's not going to be that easy.
You have to work hard for it.
You have to earn my trust.
And, when you get it,
I might just tell you everything I know.
You know, to be honest,
Jaguar doesn't really mean
anything to me right now.
Julio's the one we should focus on.
He's the one in charge,
so we must get to him first.
Why not kill two birds with one stone?
Julio and Jaguar…
I can't wait for their downfall.
And, if you do that,
I might just give you a reward.
Do you want to know what it is?
Well, do you?
Do you want to have…
a taste?
[slow tense music playing]
With all due respect, ma'am…
I couldn't care about the money.
All that matters to me
is killing Julio Ardiente and Jaguar…
so I can protect the ones I love.
That's all there is to it.
I hope we can work together.
I'll be going now.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door closes]
[sighs]
That damned woman!
She almost smashed my face in!
Smashed it in?
Then you would've looked better.
-[guffaws]
-Hey!
Want to get back at her?
How?
[scoffs]
Come.
[foreboding music playing]
All right, grab her!
[laughing]
[goon] Don't fight back.
Time to get our reward.
You better make sure
I don't get out of here alive.
Or else, I'm going to make you pay.
-[mocking laughter]
-Hurry up! Go!
Hold her tight.
Dude, hurry up!
[suspenseful music playing]
[gunshot]
[chuckles]
Party's over, boys!
Diego, son…
You have to take the position
when Julio gets ousted.
We don't know
Vice Governor Mateo Ruiz well.
Can we really trust him?
Nanny, his track record is clean.
And he's a better choice
because he's not an Ardiente.
But what about your dream
to be the governor?
Uncle, I can sacrifice my dream…
if it's for the people's freedom.
Hey, Batch, watch this.
[reporter] A truck carrying stolen rice
worth two million pesos
was seized by the police during a storm,
under the orders of Vice
Governor Mateo Ruiz.
Here's his statement.
We will subdue all thefts
here in Ardiente.
This is one of the reasons
why our province isn't truly prospering.
Big fish or two-bit hustlers,
if you're a criminal…
don't bother trying to swim here,
because I promise you…
I will catch you.
[chuckles]
The guy's pretty tough, then.
He's like a fearless action star.
Just like you. [chuckles]
He's the man we need
to take down the Ardientes.
-It looks like it.
-Yeah.
Useless morons!
And you, cowering at the back!
Useless! Idiots!
How did Ivy get away from you?
Governor, somebody helped her.
[Julio] Somebody helped her? Who?
Was it Madrigal again?! Or maybe Diego?!
It was Mrs. Emilia.
What?
[tense music playing]
Hey, Emilia.
Where are you taking me?
Hey, Ivy. Sit back and shut up.
Don't be so impatient.
And don't you just love surprises?
Come on.
Party pooper.
Impatient? You want
to see me get impatient?
You want to see a surprise?
Let me go…
so I can surprise you with
what I'm going to do to you.
Uh-uh!
No, thank you, Ivy.
But this is your day.
This is your big, big day!
This is just for you.
I'm not going to steal your thunder.
You'll be surprised.
Stay put, okay?
Relax!
We're almost there.
[mocking laugh]
[church bells ringing]
[motorcycle engines revving]
[phone ringing]
Oops, I have a phone call.
-[phone ringing]
-Oh! It's Papa.
Hello, Papa.
Emilia, Emilia…
…my she-devil of a daughter, Emilia.
According to my men,
you did something stupid again.
Papa, it was just a little prank.
And Ivy is with me right now.
[chuckles]
Where are you taking her?
Hmm…
I don't want to tell you, Papa.
Because I know you're going
to take Ivy from me again
and you'll do what you want with her.
So, I'm not going to tell you.
Emilia…
…you don't have to keep her from me.
She's my enemy too.
We both want her dead.
Look…
If you want her…
Go ahead. You can have her.
I don't mind.
It's just that…
I want Arnaldo to witness…
that woman's death.
Do you understand me?
Ooh!
Do you swear on that, Papa?
You're just gonna be an audience?
You're not gonna do anything else?
I swear on the grave of my parents.
I won't interfere.
[laughs excitedly]
Okay, Papa!
It's a done deal!
I shall see you, then.
[Emilia laughs excitedly]
[suspenseful music playing]
Woohoo!
This is it!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
We're near.
Don't celebrate just yet, Emilia,
because when I get
out of here, I'll kill you
and leave your body to rot!
Ha!
[mockingly] I'm so scared.
Yes, you should be scared!
[Emilia guffaws]
We're here!
This is it!
How did your meeting with the attorney go?
I was able to talk to the vice governor.
He said he'll consider
forming an alliance with us.
Any news about Ivy?
That's the problem, Diego.
We haven't found her yet.
What?
[unsettling music playing]
[Ivy grunting]
Stand up, Ivy! Get up!
[groans]
Move!
[Ivy panting]
Walk. Stop making a fuss!
Stop fighting!
Come here.
Well, now…
Let's see how tough you are.
What will you do to me?! Huh?!
You'll find out soon enough.
You'll see where I'm taking you, witch!
Move it!
[laughing]
[Emilia laughs boisterously]
-[Emilia sighs]
-Emilia, you witch!
Where are we?!
Oh, pipe down.
Shh!
Where are we?
Ivy, stop asking questions.
You'll know later after your last breath.
[giggles]
You witch!
-[Emilia laughs maniacally]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] It's going to be
Ivy's funeral, Papa.
Ivy is dying today?!
[Ivy] What are you doing to me?!
Let go of me!
[mockingly] No, sir, no.
Please, don't leave me, Ivy.
Please!
[fake cries, laughs maniacally]
[Raul] Ivy Aguas is in danger.
The Ardientes buried her alive.
What?
-[Camia screaming]
-[glass breaking]
They buried her alive
just like they did to me!
[Damian] Now that I'm here, I'll help you.
I'll find your daughter.
[Ivy wheezing, crying]
[theme music playing]